https://www.r1rcm.com/privacy

EMS
U.S.
Terms and Conditions of Use
Please read these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy carefully before using this site. By using the website, you accept and agree to be bound by these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. This site and its related services are governed by the Terms of Use stated below, and your continued access to this site and its services is subject to your agreement to be bound by such Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, as they may change from time to time. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, you may not use this site (the website or “Site”).
Data Collected
We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. Protecting your privacy is important to us and we want you to feel comfortable visiting the website of R1 RCM (the “Site”). Any personal or business information that you submit to us, including but not limited to your name, address, phone number, title, company name, and email address, will be used as set forth in this Privacy Policy. By using this Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as detailed in this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time-to-time. If you do not agree with any portion of this Policy, you should not use this Site. This Policy only applies to information collected through this Site and not to information collected offline or through other websites (even if linked to by this Site).
Children's Privacy
Our Site is not intended for children under 18 years of age. No one under age 18 may provide any information to or on the Site. We do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from children under the age of 18, and no part of our Site is structured to attract anyone under the age of 18. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 18, please contact us at contact@r1rcm.com, so we can immediately delete any such information.
Use of Data Provided by You
In accordance with your consent, we may use your personal information to market new products and offers from us or our business partners. This includes advertising personalized to you based on your interests. You can control how we market to you by not opting-in or by opting-out of receiving such communications, as applicable, or by following the instructions in any marketing communication. In the United States, we will assume your consent to receive information from us; however, you will be able to opt-out of receiving any such information. Outside of the United States, we will obtain your express written consent before providing you with any such information.While visiting our Site, if you provide personal information in order to receive information from us, or for any other purpose, we will collect and store that data in an environment that employs industry standard security protections. Please be aware, however, that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit or provide to us through the Site. We may use stored data to communicate with you outside of this Site regarding our revenue cycle management solutions. Any information provided by you to apply for a position posted under the Careers section of our Site shall be governed by the terms and conditions of the third party website to which you submit such information. For more detail regarding our policy on linking to third parties, please see the Terms of Use section of this policy below.
Use of Data Collection Technologies
As you navigate through and interact with the Site, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment and browsing actions. For example, R1 RCM may identify your computer by its IP address. An IP address is a unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. In addition, R1 RCM or Google may employ a cookie, which is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. These data collection technologies allow us to collect certain information about you, but do not identify you individually. We may retain third parties to help us collect and aggregate the information derived from these technologies.
Third Parties
If we partner with third parties to provide services on our behalf, we may share the information you provide on our Site, as well as information that is otherwise collected on our Site through data collection technologies (e.g., cookies) with those third parties. We may also be compelled to disclose your personal information to law enforcement or as otherwise required by law.
Google Analytics
We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this Site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this Site, what pages they visit when they do so, and information related to Site activity and internet usage. We use the information we get from Google Analytics to improve this Site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this Site, rather than your name or other identifying information. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics may place a cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this Site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google.You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this Site. By using this Site, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.We will not sell the information that you provide on our Site or permit our third party service providers to use that information for any purpose other than to provide services to us.
Special Notice to CA Residents
California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits California residents that have provided any personal information through the Site the right to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding year. We do not disclose the personal information of customers to third parties for any third party’s direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to request information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices, please send a request to contact@r1rcm.com.
Additionally, our Notice of Employment Privacy Practices can be found here.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time and will post any changes by a link from our homepage so that you always know what information we collect and how we use it. Such changes will be effective immediately upon posting and shall apply prospectively only. Please consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any important changes as they occur.This Privacy Policy is effective March 7, 2019, and it was last modified on March 6, 2019.
Contact
contact@r1rcm.com
About Us
About
Leadership
Technology Innovation
Compliance
Investors
U.S.
International
Connect
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
© 2020 R1 RCM, Inc. All rights reserved.
